<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Restora</string>
    <string name="tavsiye_metin">After a new research that had a great impact in the world of science, there were reports suggesting that people could continue to eat red meat without fear of unhealthy results. So how should we interpret these findings? Many studies to date have revealed that consuming processed or unprocessed red meat is associated with a high risk of cancer, cardiovascular problems, and premature death. Based on this and similar evidence, health guidelines have been published recommending individuals to reduce their red meat intake as much as possible. However, on October 1, 2019, an article that made headlines around the world was published in Annals of Internal Medicine, one of the leading scientific journals of medicine; The findings suggest that red meat will not have a harmful effect on health as previously thought. NutriRECS researchers explained that they need to reconsider the available evidence for red meat consumption and negative health outcomes for various reasons. In 12 randomized controlled trials, they concluded that a reduction in meat consumption, down from three to seven servings per week, was not statistically significant in reducing the risk of cancer, diabetes or heart disease. This study is based on four systematic reviews in the NutriRECS guideline that take into account various data sources and health outcomes, including overall mortality, heart health and cancer. A spokesperson for the American Cancer Society (ACS) has likened this to being said that it is safe to cycle without a helmet, although the risk has been proven. According to the diet guide developed by the 14-member international consortium, the fact that most adults consume processed and unprocessed red meat creates little health risks in the long run. The result is contrary to the rules set by the USA, which recommends a portion of red and processed meat only once a week. \"On the basis of these, we have made a weak recommendation that most people do not need to reduce their consumption of red meat or processed meat, it is certain that eating red meat or processed meat leads to cancer, diabetes or heart disease,\" said Halifax Dalhousie University professor of epidemiology and community health. as we can not say, \"he said. The authors came to the conclusion that if it is unclear whether red meat has any effect on health, if adults who eat red meat over 18 years of age love to eat red meat, insisting that they give up has little return. Consequently, this study does not completely justify consuming \"dense\" red meat or processed meat, however, it is clear that consuming red meat is not as harmful as smoking or alcohol.</string>
    <string name="tavsiye_snackbar">A study laundering consumption of red meat is on the agenda of world health news</string>
    <string name="tavsiye_baslik">Advice</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="title_activity_sefin_spesyali_tabbed">SefinSpesyaliTabbed</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Chef\'s Special 1</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Chef\'s Special 2</string>
    <string name="tab_text_3">Chef\'s Special 3</string>
    <string name="Service_Title">Restora</string>
    <string name="Service_Welcome_Message">Welcome</string>
    <string name="Service_Starting_Message">service starting</string>
    <string name="Service_Done_Message">service done</string>
    <string name="MainActivity_Invite_Message">Hey, how about dinner at Resto?</string>
    <string name="MainActivity_Invite_Where">\"Where to send the invitation:\"</string>
    <string name="Hakkimizda_Share_Body">Great restaurant, highly recommend!</string>
    <string name="Hakkimizda_Share_Subject">You should try this!</string>
    <string name="Hakkimizda_Share_With">\"Share on\"</string>
    <string name="Rezervasyon_Title">Reservation</string>
    <string name="Rezervasyon_Cancel">The change has been canceled!</string>
    <string name="Tavsiye_Close">close</string>
    <string name="Hakkimizda_Contact_Address">Contact Information and Address</string>
    <string name="MainActivity_Invite">Dinner Invitation</string>
    <string name="MainActivity_Rezervasyon">Reservation</string>
    <string name="MainActivity_Hakkimizda">About Us</string>
    <string name="MainActivity_Tavsiye">Advice</string>
    <string name="MainActivity_Sefin_spesyali">Chef\'s Special</string>
    <string name="MainActivity_Menu">Menu</string>
    <string name="Menu_Sefin_Spesyali">Did you take a look Chef\'s Special?</string>
    <string name="Rezervasyon2_Name">Your Name</string>
    <string name="Rezervasyon2_Update">Update</string>
    <string name="Rezervasyon2_Delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="Rezervasyon2_Save">Save</string>
    <string name="Rezervasyon2_Date">Enter Date (DD / MM / YYYY)</string>
    <string name="Hakkimizda_Adres">Number: +90 (232) 000 19 12 Instagram: @restora Facebook: @restora Yemek Sepeti: @restora   Navigation Drawer için ekranın solundan sağa kaydırın.</string>
    <string name="Sefin_Spesyali_Title_1">Chef\'s Special 1</string>
    <string name="Sefin_Spesyali_Body_1">Our special minced meat sauce prepared by our chef from our rested meats will be one of the indispensable parts of your refrigerator with its taste and practicality. Pasta with bolognese sauce, nacoz, taco or even minced eggs. You can make many recipes that come to your mind quickly and easily.</string>
    <string name="Sefin_Spesyali_Body2_1">Ingredients: Beef mince, Red onion, Tomato puree, Tomato paste, Cumin, Thyme, Black Pepper, Salt</string>
    <string name="Sefin_Spesyali_Detail_1">Served with a special cheese plate and red wine.</string>
    <string name="Sefin_Spesyali_Title_2">Chef\'s Special 2</string>
    <string name="Sefin_Spesyali_Body_2">\"Eggplant and tomato\" caponatali \"shrimp and calamari salad\" flavored with basil pesto provides a pleasant start to the meal. Immediately afterwards, \"Leek and pumpkin soup\" served with parmesan foccacia croutons warms you. “Plin” ravioli with ricotta and porcini mushrooms is one of the most important flavors in the menu.</string>
    <string name="Sefin_Spesyali_Body2_2">Ingredients: Beef mince, Red onion, Tomato puree, Tomato paste, Cumin, Thyme, Black Pepper, Salt</string>
    <string name="Sefin_Spesyali_Detail_2">Served with a special cheese plate and red wine.</string>
    <string name="Sefin_Spesyali_Title_3">Chef\'s Special 3</string>
    <string name="Sefin_Spesyali_Body_3">T-Bone, one of the most valuable parts of our curly lambs, contains two different meats together. One side is lamb shrinkage, the other side is lamb helmet. It is a wonderful taste with its aroma and softness. The ideal degree of cooking on the grill is medium and medium-good. Curly lambs that only graze without artificial feed, because they feed on aromatic herbs and go free in nature, both their bodies do not bind fat and their meat is pespish.</string>
    <string name="Sefin_Spesyali_Detail_3">Served with a special cheese plate and red wine.</string>
    <string name="NavHeader_Definition">A completely different flavor</string>
    <string name="NavHeader_Title">Restora</string>
    <string name="Add_Profile">Add Reservation</string>
    <string name="Drawer_Phone">Phone: +90 (012) 3456789</string>
    <string name="Drawer_Social">On Social Media: @restora</string>
    <string name="Sefin_Spesyali_Tabbed_Snackbar">These are the delicious recipes the chef chooses for you!</string>
    <string name="hakkimizda">About Us</string>
    <string name="chefs_special">Chef\'s Special</string>
    <string name="menu_et">Red Meat</string>
    <string name="menu_bira">Beer</string>
    <string name="menu_salata">Salad</string>
    <string name="menu_balik">Fish</string>
    <string name="menu_kokteyl">Cocktail</string>
    <string name="menu_sarap">Wine</string>
    <string name="Hakkimizda_Bilgi2">Restora is a business established in 2020. On this path we set out with the most delicious food motto .... Click here to learn the number of employees.</string>
    <string name="Hakkimizda_Text2">We are a huge family with 36 full-time employees and 12 part-time employees.</string>
    <string name="Hakkimizda_bilgi">Information About Us</string>
</resources>